<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">MusicalStructure</string>

    <!-- Category name for songs [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_songs">Songs</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for artists [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_artists">Artists</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for playlists [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_playlists">Playlists</string>

    <!-- Category name for the vocabulary words for Now Playing [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_nowPlaying">Now Playing</string>

    <!-- Text for Home Screen button -->
    <string name="home_screen">Home Screen</string>

    <!-- Explanation of the purpose of the Songs Activity -->
    <string name="explanation_songs">In this activity, the user can see a scrollable list of all
        his songs. The list items appear as cards with the cover at the very left of each list item,
        the song\'s name (upper half, fat letters) and the artist\'s name (lower half, smaller text
        size, more discreet color) right next to it, and the song\'s duration (in mm:ss) to the very
        right.</string>

    <!-- Explanation of the purpose of the Artists Activity -->
    <string name="explanation_artists">In this activity, the user can see a scrollable list of all
        the artists of the songs in his library. This activity should look similar to Apple\'s now
        infamous "Cover Flow".
    </string>

    <!-- Explanation of the purpose of the Playlists Activity -->
    <string name="explanation_playlists">In this activity, the user can see a scrollable list of all
        the playlists he created. The playlists are displayed as rectangular boxes with different covers
        of songs in the playlist in the upper half of the box, and the name and a user-editable
        description of it in the lower half. Plus, a "Play Now" icon overlapping both halfs in the
        lower right corner. Overall, it is similar to Google Play Music\'s playlists tab.</string>


    <!-- Explanation of the purpose of the Now Playing Activity -->
    <string name="explanation_nowPlaying">In this activity, the user can see all the info (title,
        artist, album, duration (incl. time already played and time left)) about the currently
        playing song. He also has the ability to pause and play the song from here, to skip to the
        next song or go back to the last one. To like or dislike it, so that the logic behind the
        app knows which songs to play more often and which not. There should also be the option
        to stream the song to a connected Bluetooth speaker or a Chromecast device, add it to a
        playlist and go into shuffle mode. The album cover should be front and center of the
        activity.</string>

</resources>
